University Senate; Records ua200
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Predecessor Bodies, 1915-1966; 2; 1.5 cubic ft.
  - Faculty Council, 1915-1966; 2.1; 1 cubic ft.
    - Curriculum Development, 1953-1955 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 12)
    - Memoranda, 1962-1963 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 13)
    - Minutes, 1915-1917 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 14)
    - Minutes, 1917-1925 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 15)
    - Administrative Scrapbook with Minutes, Comencement Programs, Course Information [RESTRICTED], 1917 September 17-1926 March 24 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 16)
      Conditions Governing Access
      A few pages contain student grades and must be restricted due to FERPA. Please consult an archivist for details.
    - Minutes, 1926-1937 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 17)
    - Minutes-Duplicates, 1926-1937 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 18)
    - Minutes, 1944-1949 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 19)
    - Minutes, 1949-1952 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 20)
    - Minutes, 1952-1955 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 21)
    - Minutes, 1955-1957 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 22)
    - Minutes, 1957-1959 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 23)
    - Minutes, 1959-1960 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 24)
    - Policy Documents, 1917 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 25)
    - Report of the Dispute Dr. Eson and Dr. Elbow, 1965 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 26)
    - Reports, 1940-1949 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 27)
    - Reports, 1944-1949 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 28)
    - Reports, 1944-1956 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 29)
    - Reports, 1949-1966 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 30)
    - Reports, 1950-1952 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 31)
    - Reports, 1950-1953 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 32)
    - Reports, 1950-1956 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 33)
    - Reports, 1951-1955 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 34)
    - Reports Folder 1, 1955-1957 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 35)
    - Reports Folder 2, 1955-1957 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 36)
    - Reports, 1957-1959 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 37)
    - Reports, 1958-1962 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 38)
    - Reports, 1959-1960 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 39)
    - Rules and Pland for Faculty-Administrative Council, ca. 1944-1946 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 40)
    - Reports, 1960-1963 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 41)
    - Treasurer's Reports, 1960-1964 (Box 1 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 42)
  - Academic Council, 1952-1963; 2.2; 0.5 cubic ft.
    This series consists mainly of minutes and memoranda relating to Council meetings, and includes some committee reports. Originally, the Academic Council was called the College Advisory Council (1952-53). The Academic Council, sometimes called the Administrative (Academic) Council, was an independent council composed of departmental chairs and administrative representatives. It was responsible for acting upon proposed undergraduate course changes and bringing "broad curriculum changes to the faculty for a vote." Committees of the Council included the Undergraduate Curriculum Committee, the Undergraduate Admissions Committee, Academic Standing Committee, and the Library Committee (Faculty Handbook, 1962, p. 16).
    - Minutes and Memoranda, 1952-1953 (Box 2 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 1)
    - Minutes and Memoranda, 1953-1954 (Box 2 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 2)
    - Minutes and Memoranda, 1954-1955 (Box 2 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 3)
    - Minutes and Memoranda, 1955-1956 (Box 2 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 4)
    - Minutes and Memoranda, 1956-1957 (Box 2 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 5)
    - Minutes and Memoranda, 1957-1958 (Box 2 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 6)
    - Minutes and Memoranda, 1958-1959 (Box 2 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 7)
    - Minutes and Memoranda, 1959 (Box 2 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 8)
    - Minutes and Memoranda, 1960 (Box 2 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 9)
    - Minutes and Memoranda, 1961 (Box 2 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 10)
    - Minutes and Memoranda, 1962 (Box 2 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 11)
    - Minutes and Memoranda, 1963 (Box 3 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 1)
    - Physical Education Requirements, 1963; 1965 (Box 3 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 2)
    - Reports, 1956-1963 (Box 3 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 3)
    - Reports, 1959-1960 (Box 3 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 4)
    - Reports, 1966 (Box 3 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 5)
    - Undergraduate Curriculum Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 3 (2-Predecessor Bodies), Folder 6)
- Legislation, 1966-2006; 3; 3.5 cubic ft.
  Arranged chronologically by academic year. When specific dates are listed in the title the latest action date is used (Legislation logs starting at 8485).
  Contains record copies of legislation approved by the Faculty Senate (1966-69) and the University Senate (1969-84). Each year's legislation is preceded by a summary list of the legislation for that year. The listing indicates whether the legislation was approved, sent back to committee, or rejected. See Appendixes A and B for a yearly list (1966-84) and index (1980-88) to the legislation.
  - Proposed Bills and Resolutions, 1966 May-1969 September (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - Summary of Legislation, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 2)
  - 6667-01: Establishment of Senate Councils - Approved, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-02: Protest Regarding Bachelor of Fine Arts - Tabled, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-03: Amendment to Composition of the Council on Educational Policy- Approved, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-04: Appointment of Third SUNY Senator - Approved, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-05: SUNYA Telethon for Mental Health - Tabled, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-06: Participation in College Bowl - Approved, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-07: Support for Library Budget - Approved, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-08: Amendment to Trustees Policies - Approved, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-09: Indignation- Abridgement of Students' Rights to Demonstrate Outside Polling Booth - Approved, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-10: Foreign Students' Non-Academic Problems - Withdrawn, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-11: Committee on Foreign Study - Withdrawn, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-12: Council Reports - Approved, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-13: Council on Intercollegiate Athletic Policy - Tabled, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-14: Ph.D. in Foundations of Education - Approved, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-15: Doctoral Program in Atmospheric Science - Approved, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-16: Ph. D. Requirements - Approved, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-17: Master's Program in Rehabilitation Counseling - Approved, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-18: Laboratory Science Admission Requirement - Approved, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-19: Advance Placement - Approved, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-20: "Grading" - Approved, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-21: Dropping a Course - Approved, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-22: Withdrawal - Approved, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-23: Master's Program in Educational Psychology - Approved, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-24: Master's Degree in Economics - Approved, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-25: Amendment to Faculty By-laws - Approved, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-26: Amendment to Faculty By-laws - Approved, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-27: Authority to Recommend Candidates for Degrees - Approved, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-28: Annual Report - Approved, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-29: Master's Degree Program in Inter-American Language and Area Studies, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-30: Master's Program in Education Approved of the Emotionally Disturbed Child - Approved, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-31: Annual Collection - Approved, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-32: Assessment of Faculty - Returned to Council, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-33: Advanced Placement - Approved, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-34: Faculty Salaries - Approved, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-35: Definitions and Procedures Related to Questions, Complaints, and Grievances - Approved, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-36: Selective Service - Defeated, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-37: Selective Service - Withdrawn, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 6667-38: Position Paper on Conflicts of Interest - Approved, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - Summary of Legislation, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 4)
  - 6768-01: Ph.D. in Mathematics - Approved - November 20, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 6768-02: Statement on Student Protests and Demonstrations - Approved - November 20, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 6768-03: Student Demonstrations - Approved - November 20, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 6768-04: Master's Program in Criminal Justice - Approved - December 18, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 6768-05: Ph.D. in Criminal Justice - Approved - December 18, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 6768-06: Guidelines Concerning Promotions in Rank and Continuing Appointments - Approved - December 18, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 6768-07: Resolution On Physical Education - Tabled - December 18, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 6768-08: Degree Pattern - Approved - January 15, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 6768-09: Admission of Special Treatment of Underprivileged Freshmen - Approved - January 15, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 6768-10: Ph.D. in Astronomy and Space Science - Approved - January 15, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 6768-11: Recommendations for Faculty Parking Violations - Approved - January 15, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 6768-12: Social Science Requirement - Approved - February 19, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 6768-13: Physical Education Requirement - Returned to Council - February 19 Approved - March 18, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 6768-14: R.O.T.C. - Approved - February 19, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 6768-15: Regulations for Faculty Parking - Approved - February 19, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 6768-16: University Certificate in Educational Media - Approved - March 18, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 6768-17: M.S. Degree in Educational Media - Approved - March 18, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 6768-18: Withdrawal Policy for Graduate Students - Approved - March 18, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 6768-19: Parking Appeals Committee - Approved - March 18, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 6768-20: Statement on: Committee, Council, Faculty, University - Approved - April 8, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 6768-21: New York College Bound Corporation - Approved - April 8, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 6768-22: University Certificate in Educational Psychology and Statistics - Approved - May 20, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 6768-23: Master of Arts in Studio Art and Art History - Approved - May 20, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 6768-24: Master of Science in the Teaching of English Language As a Second language - Approved - May 20, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 6768-25: Master of Science in Computer Science - Approved - May 20, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 6768-26: Annual Report to the Faculty - Approved - May 20, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 6768-27: Faculty Dues - Approved - May 20, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 6768-28: Study of Parking - Approved - May 20, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 6768-29: Assembly Bill No. 6445 and Senate Bill No. 5113 - Approved - May 20, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - Summary of Legislation, 1968-1969; 1967-1968 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 6)
  - 6869-01: Amendments to the Council Structure - Approved - May 27, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-02: Amendments to the Council Structure - Approved - May 27, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-03: Inclusion of Students on Councils - Approved - May 27, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-04: Departmental Program in Public Accounting - Approved - September 30, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-05: Student Membership on Councils - Approved - September 30, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-06: Departmental Programs - Approved - September 30, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-07: Faculty Mailing Lists - Approved - September 30, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-08: Student Membership on Councils - Approved - October 28, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-09: Amendment to the By-Laws - Approved - October 28, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-10: Changes in Grievance Procedures - Approved - October 28, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-11: Athletics Policy - Approved - October 28, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-12: Admissions Standards - Approved - November 18, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-13: Committee on Special Education Programs - Tabled - November 18, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-14: Master's Program in Curriculum Planning And Development - Approved - December 16, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-15: Ph.D. Program in Economics - Approved - December 16, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-16: General College - Approved - December 16, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-17: Enrollment Conditions - Approved - December 16, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-18: Requirements for the B.A. Degree - Returned to Council - December 16, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-19: Establishment of Department of Afro-American Studies - Approved - January 20, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-20: Course Scheduling - Approved - January 20, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-21: Grading - Approved - January 20, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-22: Requirements for the B.A. Degree (Speech Requirement) - Approved - January 20, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-23: Revision in EPC Charge - Approved - February 17, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-24: Agendas for Faculty Meetings - Defeated - February 17, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-25: Presidential Search - Approved - February 17, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-26: Proposals for New Programs - Approved - February 17, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-27: "Open Recruitment" policy - Approved - March 17, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-28: NYS Senate Bill 524 - Approved - February 18, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-29: Election of Graduate Students - Tabled - March 17, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-30: Departmental Programs - Approved - March 17, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-31: Requirements for the Baccalaureate Degree - Tabled - March 17, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-32: Student Awards and Opportunities for Advanced Study - No Record, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-33: Revision in the Undergraduate Academic Council's Charge - Approved - March 17, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-34: Research Policy - Tabled - March 17 - Returned to Council - April 21, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-35: Ph.D. Program in Educational Psychology - Approved - April 21, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-36: Conference on Undergraduate Teaching - Approved - May 12, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-37: Provision for Faculty-Student Consultation in Schools and Departments - Approved - May 12, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-38: Calendar - Approved - May 12, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-39: Foreign Language Requirement - Approved - May 12, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-40: Discrimination in the Construction Fund and Dormitory Authority - Approved - May 12, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-41: Establishment of the Committee on Governance - Approved - June 2, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-42: Amendment to the By-laws - Approved - June 2, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-43: M.A. in Anthropology - Approved - June 2, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-44: Application of Regulations to GSPA Students - Approved - June 2, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-45: Grading - Returned to Council - June 5, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-46: Charge to the Undergraduate Acadmic Council - Approved - June 5, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-47: Student Awards - Approved - June 5, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-48: B.A. in Anthropology - Approved - June 5, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-49: B.A. in Italian - Approved - June 5, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-50: B.A. in Greek - Approved - June 5, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-51: B.A. in American Studies - Approved - June 5, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-52: B.A. in Afro-American Studies - Approved - June 5, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-53: Guidelines for the Administration of Trustees Policies - Approved - June 5, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-54: Guidelines for Granting the Rank of Professor Emeritus - Approved - June 5, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-55: Resolution for Matters Concerning Student Grades - Returned to Council - June 5, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-56: Resolution for Guidelines for Department Chairmen's Obligation Regarding Term Appointments - Returned to Council - June 5, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 6869-57: Optional Salary Payment Questions - Returned to Council - June 5, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - Proposed Bills and Resolutions, 1969 November-1971 December (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 8)
  - Summary of Legislation, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 9)
  - 6970-01: Collection of Faculty Dues - Approved - September 29, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-02: Grading System - Approved - October 27, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-03: Parking - Approved - October 27, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-04: Disciplinary Removal from Residence - Approved - October 27, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-05: Report of the Ad Hoc Faculty- Student Consultation Committee - Returned to Committee - October 27 - Approved - February 16, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-06: Inter-Institutional Registration - Approved - November 17, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-07: Report from the CPCA - Tabled - November 17, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-08: Recommendations of the Ad Hoc Faculty- Student Consultation Committee - Tabled - November 17, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-09: Albany High School Incident - Withdrawn - November 17, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-10: Discriminary Practices - Withdrawn - November 17, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-11: Guidelines for use of Campus Facilities for Demonstrations - Defeated - November 17, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-12: Further Guidelines - Approved - November 17, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-13: Class Scheduling - Approved - December 15, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-14: Vietnam Intervention - Approved - February 9, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-15: Revision in the Requirements for the B.A. and B.S. - Approved - February 16, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-16: Revision in the B.A. and B.S. Requirements - Approved - February 16, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-17: B.A. in Comparative Literature - Approved - February 16, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-18: M.A. in Geography - Approved - February 16, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-19: Recommendations by the CPCA to the Senate - Returned to Council - February 16, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-20: Requirements for the B.A. and B.S. - Approved - February 16, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-21: Senate Action of February 9, 1970 - Approved - February 16, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-22: Parking - Referred to PPC - February 16, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-23: Reactivation of RPA Committee - Referred to Senex - February 16, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-24: Personal Records - Referred to SAC - February 16, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-25: War-related Research - Referred to Council - February 16, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-26: Recruitment on Campus - Referred to Council - February 16 - Defeated - March 16, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-27: Signature of Advisor - Referred to Council - February 16, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-28: Cancellation of Classes and "Dialogue" - Approved - March 16, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-29: EOP Grading - Approved - March 16, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-30: Business Education Requirements - Approved - for Admission March 16, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-31: Physical Education Requirement - Approved - March 16, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-32: NASPA Resolution - Approved - March 16, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-33: Melville-Steinmetz Housing - Approved - March 16, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-34: Binghamton Resolution - Referred to Council - March 16, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-35: Senate Membership, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-36: Jurisdiction of the Senate - Postponed Indefinitely - April 20, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)